and and you start serving you start serving this is how this person i believe how can i be a
resource to you how can i what do you mean how can i so then you become a people pleaser and
you're like but i'm not a people pleaser i say no all the time it's like yeah but you're stretching
like you're thinking all the time about how to show them the best way for this person like
you're thinking about their success like you're thinking about like how can they win you think
about how they can win on your time so you start doing these things that are really attached to
the fact that when you were young you were let you were left and you don't ever want to feel that
way again and so you're reacting in ways that at one point protected you but are no longer helpful
to you they're detrimental to you because it's attaching you to people that are actually going
to harm you again shit
you